const TribalMovements = [
	{
		questionText: 'Sanyasi Vidhroh',
		ans: ['Anandh Math-Bankin chandra Chaterjee'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Anandh Math',
		ans: ['Bankin chandra Chaterjee'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Ahom Uprisng',
		ans: ['Ghom Ghar Kuvar', 'Bengal'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Pagal Panti Vidhroh',
		ans: ['Karam shan & then Tipu', 'Bengal'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Farazi Vidhroh',
		ans: ['Haji Shariatullah & Dadu Mian', 'Bengal'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Chaur Uprisng',
		ans: ['Durjan Singh', 'Bengal'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Khasi Vidhroh',
		ans: ['Tirat Singh', 'Meghalaya'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Ramosi Vidhroh',
		ans: ['Chitar singh', 'M.H'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Kuka Vidhroh',
		ans: ['Bhajat Jawahal Mal', 'punjab'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Kol Uprising',
		ans: ['Buddha Bhagat', 'Jharkhand'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Santhal Vidhroh',
		ans: ['Sindhu kanu', 'Jharkhand'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Munda Vidhroh',
		ans: ['Birsa Munda', 'Jharkhand'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'which Vidhroh is also known as "Ulgulam"/"Great Tumlut"?',
		ans: ['Munda Vidhroh'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Paika Rebellion',
		ans: ['Durgan singh', 'Odisa'],
	},

];

export default TribalMovements;
